After a
long day.
I have
my own
ways of
unwinding.
And let's
just say
it always
ends on
a high
note.
There are
nights when
ordinary just
won't do.
For those
moments,
there's Durex
Slide and
Ride, a
premium sleeve
designed to
make every
second alone
feel more
indulgent,
more intense.
It feels
real,
velvetly soft,
with a
textured grip
outside
and sensual
dots inside.
It builds
friction
exactly where
you crave
it the
most.
Every moment,
every bass,
every
listens to
you,
moves with
becomes yours
to control.
And it's
waterproof so
that when
the water
turns hot,
so can
your experience.
This isn't
just an
upgrade,
it's a
whole new
level of
pleasure.
Slide into
something more
satisfying on
durexindia.com before
anybody else
does.